[
  {
    "type": "choose",
    "problems": [
      {
        "question": "Upset the apple cart",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "расстроить кого-то",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "испортить урожай",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "сорвать планы",
            "accuracy": "c"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Sour grapes",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "глупый поступок",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "притворное пренебрежение",
            "accuracy": "c"
          },
          {
            "text": "грустное выражение лица",
            "accuracy": "w"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Cherry-pick",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "выбор только хорошего без учета всего",
            "accuracy": "c"
          },
          {
            "text": "правильный выбор",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "неразумный выбор",
            "accuracy": "w"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Bad apple",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "неприятный человек",
            "accuracy": "c"
          },
          {
            "text": "глупый поступок",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "плохо-сделанная работа",
            "accuracy": "w"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you like them apples?",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "что из этого ты выберешь?",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "как тебе такое?",
            "accuracy": "c"
          },
          {
            "text": "как я выгляжу?",
            "accuracy": "w"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Top banana",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "идеальный человек",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "эгоистичный человек",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "лидер",
            "accuracy": "c"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Go pear-shaped",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "завидовать",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "пойти не так",
            "accuracy": "c"
          },
          {
            "text": "сделать аккуратно",
            "accuracy": "w"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Life is a bowl of cherries",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "скучная жизнь",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "жизнь полная загадок",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "прекрасная жизнь",
            "accuracy": "c"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Polish (one’s) apple",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "льстить",
            "accuracy": "c"
          },
          {
            "text": "улучшить отношения с кем-то",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "помочь кому-то",
            "accuracy": "w"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "The apple of my eye",
        "variants": [
          {
            "text": "увиденное своими глазами",
            "accuracy": "w"
          },
          {
            "text": "зеница ока",
            "accuracy": "c"
          },
          {
            "text": "чувство прекрасного",
            "accuracy": "w"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "connect",
    "problems": [
      {
        "id": "1",
        "letter": "a",
        "part1": "As American as",
        "part2": "pick",
        "answer": "d"
      },
      {
        "id": "2",
        "letter": "b",
        "part1": "Speak with a plum in",
        "part2": "job",
        "answer": "c"
      },
      {
        "id": "3",
        "letter": "c",
        "part1": "Apples and",
        "part2": "mouth",
        "answer": "e"
      },
      {
        "id": "4",
        "letter": "d",
        "part1": "Cherry-",
        "part2": "apple pie",
        "answer": "a"
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "letter": "e",
        "part1": "Go",
        "part2": "oranges",
        "answer": "h"
      },
      {
        "id": "6",
        "letter": "f",
        "part1": "Sour",
        "part2": "apple",
        "answer": "j"
      },
      {
        "id": "7",
        "letter": "g",
        "part1": "Peaches and",
        "part2": "cream",
        "answer": "g"
      },
      {
        "id": "8",
        "letter": "h",
        "part1": "Life is a bowl of",
        "part2": "bananas",
        "answer": "i"
      },
      {
        "id": "9",
        "letter": "i",
        "part1": "A plum",
        "part2": "cherries",
        "answer": "b"
      },
      {
        "id": "10",
        "letter": "j",
        "part1": "Bad",
        "part2": "grapes",
        "answer": "f"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "text",
    "problems": [
      [
        {
          "text": "You can’t compare these two companies. They are just"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "apples and oranges",
            "sour grapes",
            "bad apples"
          ],
          "answer": "apples and oranges"
        },
        {
          "text": "."
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "I always"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "speak with a plum in my mouth",
            "compare apples and oranges",
            "go bananas"
          ],
          "answer": "go bananas"
        },
        {
          "text": "when you don’t pick up the phone."
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "Mary has a talent for singing and playing the piano, just like her mother. Indeed,"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "apple polisher",
            "the apple doesn’t falls far from the tree",
            "life is a bowl of cherries"
          ],
          "answer": "the apple doesn’t falls far from the tree"
        },
        {
          "text": "."
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "Above all, we note that, if things"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "upset the apple cart",
            "go bananas",
            "go pear-shaped"
          ],
          "answer": "go pear-shaped"
        },
        {
          "text": ", we can rely on our friends."
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "Look, he's not trying to"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "bite at the cherry",
            "upset the apple cart",
            "cherry-pick"
          ],
          "answer": "upset the apple cart"
        },
        {
          "text": "— he just wants to help us."
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "Since she got that"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "plum job",
            "top banana",
            "bad apple"
          ],
          "answer": "plum job"
        },
        {
          "text": "with the bank, she is been buying a second home. "
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "The team, hoping for a second"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "plum job",
            "banana",
            "bite at the cherry"
          ],
          "answer": "bite at the cherry"
        },
        {
          "text": "prepared extensively for the competition."
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "He doesn't want to be a"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "second banana",
            "top banana",
            "the apple of my eye"
          ],
          "answer": "second banana"
        },
        {
          "text": ", he wants to be the best. "
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "She has such a"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "sour grapes",
            "peaches and cream",
            "cherry-pick"
          ],
          "answer": "peaches and cream"
        },
        {
          "text": "hair."
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "text": "Brian always"
        },
        {
          "variants": [
            "go pear-shaped",
            "polishes apple",
            "go bananas"
          ],
          "answer": "polishes apple"
        },
        {
          "text": "with his boss because he's hoping for a promotion."
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "translate",
    "problems": [
      {
        "question": "Яблоко от яблони недалеко падает",
        "answer": "The apple never falls far from the tree"
      },
      {
        "question": "Все испортить",
        "answer": "Upset the apple cart"
      },
      {
        "question": "Подлинно американское",
        "answer": "As American as apple pie"
      },
      {
        "question": "Иметь характерное для высших слоёв общества произношение",
        "answer": "Speak with a plum in mouth"
      },
      {
        "question": "Шанс или возможность",
        "answer": "A bite at the cherry"
      },
      {
        "question": "Льстец",
        "answer": "Apple polisher"
      },
      {
        "question": "Свести кого-то с ума",
        "answer": "To drive someone bananas"
      },
      {
        "question": "Зеница ока",
        "answer": "The apple of my eye"
      },
      {
        "question": "Как тебе такое?",
        "answer": "How do you like them apples?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Хорошая работа",
        "answer": "A plum job"
      }
    ]
  }
]